Mental Health Association in New York State, Inc. (MHANYS) Records apap131
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Programs, 1981-2001; 14; 1.17 cubic ft.
  - Sexual Abuse, 1994-2000; 14.12; 0.15 cubic ft.
    - Rape Crisis Proposal, 1997 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 53-54)
    - Response to RFP, 1997 (Box 1 (14-Programs), Folder 55-56)
    - Sexual Abuse Database, 1994 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 1)
    - Sexual Abuse Survivors Resource Center, 1994-1996 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 2)
    - Survivors' Forum, 1994 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 3-4)
    - Task Force Networker, 2000 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 5)
    - Trauma Task Forces, listing by county, 2000 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 6)
  - Transitions Training, 1999-2001; 14.13; 0.15 cubic ft.
    The Transitions Training subseries includes documents related to this training program prepared by MHANYS for the New York State Office of Mental Health serving persons with mental illness returning to their communities from state prisons.
    - The Clinical Impact of Doing Time: Mental Illness and Incarceration, 1999 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 7)
    - Contracts, 1999-2001 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 8)
    - Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 9)
    - Satellite Broadcast, 1999-2001 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 10)
    - Training Workshop Participants, 2000 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 11)
    - Transitions Project, 2000 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 12)
    - Transitions Project, 2001 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 13)
  - Work Study Program, 1967-1971; 14.14; 1 folder
    The Work Study Program for students in mental health was co-sponsored by MHANYS and the State University of New York (SUNY) under which students from the State University of New York at Albany carried out paid or volunteer work in mental health institutions or community centers while taking related courses and seminars at the university.
    - Student Intern Program, 1967-1971 (Box 2 (14-Programs), Folder 8)